{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311121034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311121034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311131285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311131284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311132039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311132039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMOJA"," userResponse":" KIMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311132883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311132883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311133591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311133591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311133815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311133814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311134495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311134495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311135267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311135266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311138426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311138425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311138981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311138980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311139755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311139755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311140010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311140009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311140757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311140756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311143635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311143635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311144473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311144472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311145296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311145295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" WALILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311145474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311145474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311146240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311146239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311149747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311149747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311150595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311150594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONYWA"," userResponse":" ALIONYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311150787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311150786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311151724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311151724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311152770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311152769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIINGIE"," userResponse":" ASIINGIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311153760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311153760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311156959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311156958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311158289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311158287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPUUZA"," userResponse":" ALIPUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311159029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311159028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" USHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311159243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311159242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311159943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311159942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311162986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311162985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311163499","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311163499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311164352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311164352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311165348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311165348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311168449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311168448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311169556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311169555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311169780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311169779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311170355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311170354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311173996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311173996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" ALIMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311175023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311175022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311175129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311175129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311175683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311175683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311179309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311179308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAMIWA"," userResponse":" ALIVAMIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311179476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311179476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311180231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311180230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311181246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311181245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMLA"," userResponse":" WAKAMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311184518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311184518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311185317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311185316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311186474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311186473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUMTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311189633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311189632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311190297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311190297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311191740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311191740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311192255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311192254"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311193322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311193322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311194189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311194188"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311195156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311195155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311198795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311198794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" WALIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311199420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311199420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311200128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311200127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELIWA"," userResponse":" AMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311200332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311200331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311200942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311200941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311203662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311203661"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311203743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311203743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" 15d69b22-2e40-4e20-a37c-f554f7e68be9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311212107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311212107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-V-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311215445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311215445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_I-F-W"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311218593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311218593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_T-F-O"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311225408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311225408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Y-J-F"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311240870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311240870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_A-T-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311248981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311248981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-S-E"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311287103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311287103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_M-F-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311357079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311357079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_H-F-V"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311361670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311361670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_G-O-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311365352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311365352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_W-F-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311371086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311371086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_F_W-F-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311379930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311379930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" c32bcdf6-a006-4ea5-8a71-1c49539f4376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_F_W-F-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311388183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311388183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" cce9f542-6abc-47bd-9674-a24cc3fad2a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-B"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311396592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311396592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092508"," gameId":" cce9f542-6abc-47bd-9674-a24cc3fad2a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_L-F-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}